https://acoach4u.com/privacy-policy/

HomeCoaching ServicesLife & Personal Coaching
Services For IndividualsEntrepreneurs and Small Business CoachingExecutive
Coaching & Leadership DevelopmentCoaching for Financial Planners & AdvisorsAbout CoachingBenefits of Working with a Business Coach (or Life Coach, Executive Coach, etc.)The Coaching ProcessLife Coaching QuestionnaireHow To Choose A Life Or Business CoachYour Life Purpose?Emotional Intelligence CoachingCoaching Fees & PoliciesFor CoachesMentoring, Skill Development And Supervision SupportAccelerated 1 to 1
Business Development SupportFree Info, Resources & Marketing Help For Life, Business & Executive CoachesMarketing Essentials for Coaches E-book (PDF)Steve’s Top 10 Tips On Marketing
For CoachesHow To Become A Happy And Successful Life, Business or Executive CoachAbout SteveGet To Know Executive Business Life Coach SteveSteve Mitten’s Photo GalleryClient Success StoriesClient TestimonialsWhy Choose
Business & Executive Leadership Coach Steve?ResourcesLife and Business Coaching Reference BooksSteve’s Newsletter ArchiveArticles by SteveLife Coach Sites Of InterestContactConnect with steveEmailFacebookGoogle+LinkedInTwitterYouTube SearchGeneral I completely honor your privacy. I do not share, sell, or otherwise disclose any personal information, contact information, emails etc. And I will never flood your inbox with info you do not want. (I rarely send out more than 3 newsletters a year.)Unsubscribe Policy Should you wish to unsubscribe to my newsletter, there is a link on every edition that will allow you to do so.  And, if you have any problem, simply send me an email with unsubscribe in the subject line.All Personal Information All personal information is kept private to the best of my ability in double password protected files.Linked Sites I provide links to other sites I think might be of general interest to you.  However I cannot provide any guarantee regarding their privacy policies and so you must proceed at your own risk.Questions If you have any questions about my Privacy Policy please send me an email. Satisfaction GuaranteeYou should get great value out of every single coaching session. If not, you are free to leave at any time. I do not require you to commit to, or pay in advance, for months of coaching.Coach Steve Mitten 2007 "Coach of the Year" **2005 President, International Coach Federation5 Start-up/ 2 IPO Entrepreneur, Engineer, Coach and Mentor with a Passion For Helping Leaders and Business Owners To Grow, Raise Their Awareness, and Achieve Far More Meaningful Success. Assisting Clients in: Transitions, Business and Leadership Development, Emotional Intelligence, Positive Psychology (Happiness), Neuroscience, Mentoring, Mindfulness and Spiritual Development. Certification LogosHow to make important changes
Stay ConnectedIf you would like to keep in touch, and see my regular posts and videos, please simply follow me on my Facebook Business Page. Free info Most RequestedNewsletter & Article ArchiveHow to Become a CoachFree Info & Resources for CoachesUpcoming Programs Key PagesInfo, Resources & Marketing Help For Life, Business & Executive CoachesHow to Become a CoachLife & Personal Coaching
Services For IndividualsEntrepreneurs & Small BusinessExecutive
Coaching & Leadership DevelopmentCoaching for Financial Planners & AdvisorsOther PagesSitemapPrivacy PolicyContact SteveCertifications
